Now at the end of this course,
بنهاية الدورة،
you'll be responsible for completing a project.
سوف تكون مسؤولًا عن إكمال مشروع.
The goals of the project are for you to be able
وسوف تكون أهداف هذا المشروع متروكة لك لتكون قادرًا
to implement what we learned in this course.
على تطبيق ما تعلمته في هذه الدورة.
To ultimately find and apply for freelance jobs by creating a process to source clients.
وهو كيف تكون قادرًا على إيجاد والتقدم للأعمال الحرة عن طريق إنشاء طريقة لإيجاد العملاء.
Use best practices to go through a project scope and choose a pricing framework,
وكيف تستخدم أفضل الممارسات للخوض في نطاق المشروع واختيار الإطار التسعيري،
aligning with clients' needs.
وكيف تُوائم احتياجات العميل.
Manage projects by maximizing value for the client.
وكيف تدير المشاريع بتحقيق أقصى استفادة للعميل.
Finally, formally closing out a project and secure payments.
وأخيرًا، كيف تنهي المشروع رسميًا وتؤمن استلام مستحقاتك.
During the project, you will work with
أثناء المشروع سوف تعمل مع
a mock client to practice the initial communication stages.
عميل صوري لممارسة مراحل التواصل الأولية معه.
Learn how to manage the client's project by utilizing the project management process,
وسوف تتعلم كيف تدير مشروع العميل عن طريق الاستفادة من عملية إدارة المشاريع
through a tool called Trello,
من خلال أداة تدعى Trello،
as well as setting up project milestones.
وأيضًا كيف تضع الخطوات المرحلية للمشروع.
Invoicing your client.
وكيف تعد فاتورة للعميل.
This will get you comfortable with interacting with clients,
سيجعلك هذا تشعر بالراحة في التعامل مع العملاء،
as well as going through project stages,
وأيضًا في الخوض في مراحل المشروع
from initial communication to final payment.
بداية من الاتصال الأولي وحتى الدفعة الأخيرة.
Now the project will require you to read a project listing,
سوف يتطلب منك المشروع أن تقرأ قائمة بالمشاريع،
write an initial expression of interests message to a client,
وأن تكتب رسالة تعبير عن اهتمام أولية لعميل،
set up a project management process,
وأن تضع عملية إدارة للمشروع،
create a Trello board with outlined project milestones.
وأن تنشئ لوحة Trello موضحًا فيها الخطوات المرحلية للمشروع.
Finally, invoice the client by using a provided invoicing template.
وأخيرًا، أن تعد فاتورة للعميل باستخدام نموذج الفاتورة المقدم.